<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Abhirath Batra</title><link>https://abhirathb.github.io/</link><description>Recent content on Abhirath Batra</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Sun, 01 May 2022 16:57:49 +0530</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://abhirathb.github.io/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Abhirath</title><link>https://abhirathb.github.io/authors/abhirath/</link><pubDate>Sun, 01 May 2022 16:57:49 +0530</pubDate><guid>https://abhirathb.github.io/authors/abhirath/</guid><description>ELt&amp;rsquo;s see</description></item><item><title>Organisation of posts</title><link>https://abhirathb.github.io/posts/test/</link><pubDate>Thu, 28 Apr 2022 23:28:53 +0530</pubDate><guid>https://abhirathb.github.io/posts/test/</guid><description>This is how posts are organised on this site :
Substack contains regularly written newsletter. Older posts are in Archive This section is for things that I want to be more permenant and not lost in the serialised nature of a newsletter.</description></item><item><title>Protein folding &amp; The AI 'Solution' : A primer for non-scientists</title><link>https://abhirathb.github.io/archive/protien-folding/</link><pubDate>Mon, 30 Nov 2020 00:00:00 +0530</pubDate><guid>https://abhirathb.github.io/archive/protien-folding/</guid><description>TLDR Just yesterday, Deepmind published a blog talking about how their AI, AlphaFold2, predicted protein structures in the biennial CASP challenge this year with stunning accuracy. There&amp;rsquo;s been a lot of buzz in the computational science community discussing the ramifications of their work.
If you&amp;rsquo;ve seen the buzz and are curious about protein folding, read on&amp;hellip; This post is supposed to capture the motivation and complexity of the problem for an audience familiar with STEM in some way.</description></item><item><title>I build therefore I am!</title><link>https://abhirathb.github.io/archive/i-build-therefore-i-am/</link><pubDate>Wed, 30 Sep 2020 00:00:00 +0530</pubDate><guid>https://abhirathb.github.io/archive/i-build-therefore-i-am/</guid><description>What am I doing?! I have spent my time, since around 2016, rapidly changing ambitions, streams, career directions, roles, and the entire narrative around what I want to do with my life. I tried everything from being the contrarian who rejected the game of the system only to be a bar-stool philosopher, to an aspiring PhD candidate who would reject the evils of corporations to push the boundaries of what humans know, to a wide-eyed employee at a startup looking to make impact.</description></item></channel></rss>